Why do any of them care?
I deserve to die like this.
Why can't they see I'm not
worth risking their lives for?
We, the second division of the Whitebeard
Pirates, will save our commander,
Ace, no matter what the cost. Yeah!
Please don't do this.
Just stop.
Just let me die like I'm supposed to.
Ace!
You're my brother!
You can't be this stupid.
Stop, Luffy.
Turn around, Bobbs.
What is it, Ace?
I'm ready.
Ready to accept whatever I deserve.
I'll accept any help that's offered to me.
But I'll also accept any punishment.
Either one, whichever comes first.
I'm just ready for all this to end.
Every time the rain no longer falls.
And I see the sky.
I think back to when I was a child.
Who could only cry.
Blindly chasing after him.
I fall far behind my only thought.
One day I will be stronger.
Grattery and gratitude
fading with the wind.
Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure, but until I do.
My voyage will not end.
No matter what's next.
I'm walking straight ahead.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything.
Will take what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me.
Push me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through.
No matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest thoughts
of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on us.
I will never let it pull us down.
We may fall, but we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way everything will
take what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
Look at that punk.
It's like he's trying to steal the show.
Like this is his war.
It should be captain. Fuggies.
I think it's time, boss.
You gotta stand up and
show the world who you are.
This is the perfect.
Moment for you to defeat Whitebeard.
Maybe I will.
I gotta keep stalling.
This war is.
Completely bonkers.
It's nothing but monsters on both sides.
I'll just keep my head
down and stay. Quiet.
Hey, you clown nose.
What the hell did you just say to me?
Are you cruising for a bruising, punk?
I take it back.
I thought I recognized you.
You worked for Roger back
when you were just a brat.
It's been a while, but it doesn't look
like things have changed too much.
I can't believe I just threatened him.
He's gonna kill me.
Yep, he's a dead man.
His only chance is to run.
Holy crap, it's Whitebeard.
And he's speaking to him.
That is like the coolest
thing I've ever seen.
It's just further proof that
you're a genuine living lover.
Don't they realize I'm about to die?
Must be nice if it's not
your ass on the line?
You've got an entire
battalion of prisoners.
Now you're not planning on
challenging me, are you?
Yeah, we meet at last.
Now prepare yourself.
Jeez, he's pushing his luck
right off the edge of a cliff.
Oh yeah, it doesn't bother me
if you're hungry for a fight.
But if you beat me, then what's next?
Might be more Navy soldiers
than you can handle on your own.
Ah hell, if I'm being honest,
they're more than I can handle.
Now, I'm not one to back
down from a challenge,
but it would make more
sense to form an alliance.
Once we're done, then you can kick my ass!
Oh, holy crap!
Whitebeard actually recognizes
you as his brother-in-arms!
He considers you an equal!
No, he called him a brat
like one minute ago!
Don't tell me you're gonna
try to take on the Navy!
You don't really think
you can win, do you?
Well, yeah, I've just gotta go all out
He's completely lost his
grip on reality! Seriously?
Oh, I've got goosebumps!
You know what?
Maybe I can do this!
Maybe I really was destined to be
king, standing on top of the world!
I think you might be onto something.
Let's join forces and take down the Navy.
This is amazing!
Man, it's too much!
Alright, you win, Whitebeard.
I'll partner with you, but only
because you're begging me to.
Huh?
So arrogant!
Oh well, that's Captain Bobby!
Well, that guy is unbelievably
easy to manipulate.
He's a fool, to say the least.
But the prisoners he's got behind
him are something else entirely.
The last thing we need
now is more enemies.
Now, back to the war.
It's too late now!
They can't stop us from charging the bay!
Right!
Now's our chance to finally join
Pops at the center of the fight!
Click.
Come in, this is Whitebeard.
Put Squared on the line, now.
Oh, Pops!
You need Captain Squared?
Well, he, um, he was right here just
a few moments ago, but now, uh...
The thing is, I'm not
seeing him anywhere, sir!
Yeah, go figure.
All that tough talk, and then he's not
even around when you ask for his help.
Hmm.
Well, so it goes.
Get me the DeKalvin Brothers, then.
Hey, Pops, what's up?
Yeah, Pops, what's up?
I want you to follow my lead.
Take command of all pirate
divisions around you.
Really?
That's straight from Pops?
Well, all right, then.
I can take the right side.
I got it.
We'll take the left side.
Right. Understood.
We'll join in on the right side, too.
Okay, if that's what Pops wants.
My ship can take any direction.
Whatever works best.
Swart's missing.
No, I haven't seen him lately.
How unusual.
Sure thing.
We'll take the left flank.
Excuse me, Fleet Admiral, sir.
But the Pirates of the New World
have altered their battle tactics.
Yes, but it seems they've
turned to their sides.
They suddenly started attacking
the approaching Navy ships.
Your bluff's been called.
Whitebeard must have
sensed something's wrong.
So I tried a cheap trick
and he didn't fall for it.
I'll admit it was a bit too obvious.
But still, he can't prevent the
inevitable just because he sees it coming.
Death!
Wee-haw!
Yee-haw!
Whoa, Eva, you're all right.
Eva, we've got to clear these
jerks out to get to Ace. Jeep it!
Fish mine karate. Yeah?
And Gum-Gum!
Five thousand brick fish. Wee!
Fasuka!
On we go!
Ah, Straw Hat, you don't really
think you can get past me.
Him again?
I shall be your opponent this time.
What are you talking about?
My karate skills will be more
than adequate to thwart you alone.
That's a mighty fine speech.
I'm impressed. Yes.
But that's good, because once I take care
of you, my zombies can run wild again.
You keep moving, Luffy.
Don't waste a moment on this villain.
I won't.
Thanks a lot, Jinbei.
Oh, man, I liked it better
when Jinbei was on our side.
It's my shadow.
Now, suffer damnation, Navy soldiers.
For your shadow shall fight for me.
You'll see how smug you are
when I turn you into sushi.
And I'm going to add your
shadow to my collection.
You'll spend the rest of your
life toiling within my darkness.
How does that sound?
I'll take that shadow now.
FISHMAN CORROTTALE!
Sharkskin bob for us!
And shark brick fist!
In the end you gave up those coveted
shadows of yours rather easily.
Perhaps you should train yourself more.
It's time you gave up and let me pass.
I'm done with you.
My only concern is ace.
You don't get to lecture me.
This fun's not over?
That's Straw Hat!
Move to Shiki!
Jeez!
It's you!
Smokey!
I finally found you.
About time. Oh, yeah.
I forgot this weapon is tipped
with sea prism stone, that cheater.
Fine. Second gear.
I'm not going to let
you get away this time.
Come, come.
Check.
Got me!
White launcher!
You're a lot stronger than you used to be.
You're strong.
He's vanished!
He's fast.
Where is he?
Seems I can return the compliment.
You're a real force to be reckoned with.
Hate to tell you, though, you're
still not strong enough to beat me.
You cheap jerk! Move that thing!
After all this time, I
finally understand the truth.
I know why Dragon really helped you.
If it weren't for him
that day, you'd be dead.
You may have had Dragon to save you in
Loguetown, but no one's gonna save you today.
This sucks.
Get your filthy hands off him!
My body's smoke, how'd she hit me?
You can't just kick him,
he ate a loggia fruit!
Wait a sec, why did the pirate
empress just save Straw Hat?
Hey Hancock, what the
hell's wrong with you?
Don't tell me you're resigning
from the warlords Shut your mouth!
The screaming fury in my heart has
rendered me deaf to your words How
dare you pin my beloved down with
your boorish club and threaten him?
You will die for your actions.
I've never felt this
angry in my entire life.
I'll feed you piece by
piece to wild animals.
The Kucha's Haki is overwhelming.
Thanks, Hancock.
Of course.
Also, I'm happy you got
my name right again.
Please, listen. That's enough.
Kuma look it's me have
you forgotten my face if
you don't stop friendship
be damned i will fight!
Back i don't know what
kind of a history you
two have but it doesn't
matter trust me Empire!
Ivankov there's really
no use in talking to
him as he is now
doflamingo what do you say?
Is something wrong with
him you're clearly a
friend of bartholomew
kuma's so i doubt you'll
take this well the man
you knew as the tyrant
kuma is not the man you see before you now
because that man is dead
but that can't be true!
How can kuma be dead?
What the hell just happened?
I thought Hancock was
supposed to be on our side?
Take this!
It's the key to your brother's handcuffs.
The touch of his hands.
They're strong.
Yet so kind.
Hancock.
Yay!
You're so awesome.
I can hug you forever!
I'll never forget this.?
What a pal!
Oh, um, well?
It's really no trouble at all.
I'm just glad I could help out.
Never mind me, though, Lupi.
Just go and save Ace.
Oh, yeah, right.
Thanks again!
No way!
He managed to defeat the
pirate empress! Unreal!
The stare did nothing.
He's a beast!
This is...
what people call...
what they call marriage.
Yeah.
Stay back, you fool!
You shall not pass on my watch.
Geez, the Empress is
really looking down on him!
Looking down so far?
She started looking up.
Get out of my way, pirate.
You know what happens to
people who betray the Navy?
Well, do you, woman?
I'll do whatever I like,
and you will allow it.
Because I'm beautiful.
It's the exact thing I need.
Impossible!
Kuma is dead?
Then who's that big guy
standing behind you?
Stop spouting nonsense.
You can't deceive me.
It's Eva.
And that big guy from before!
So, uh, were you guys
friends or something?
We were, but he's not acting like himself.
I'm sure this is a lovely
trip down memory lane for you,
but I'm afraid the Kuma you
know is no longer with us.
This is the new model new
model what do you think
he's talking about he
wants to get under my skin?
Yeah okay he's acting
pretty different than usual
right now but he's still
kuma wake up buddy hey!
Are you deaf or just stupid?
Trust me it's no use
trying to talk to him!
It happened just a few days.
ago. Dr.
Vegapunk, the government scientist,
finally finished his modifications on Kuma.
Now he's the ruthless weapon of death
he should have been from the start.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
former Bartholomew Kuma.
Doc Vegapunk? Mods?
What the hell are you talking about?
Kuma here volunteered
to be a guinea pig in
a study to build the
ultimate human weapon,
run by the government, of course.
First, they modified his
hands, then his legs.
Although his mind was still intact,
they modified his body
piece by piece until he
was no longer the same
Kuma you know and love.
But that's nonsense!
Kuma always hated the
government, you jerk!
As if he'd ever sacrifice
himself for their stupid plan!
Hey, Kuma!
Snap out of it!
It's me!
Stop yelling.
It's starting to get on my nerves.
I don't know what kind of deal
he had with the government.
He was just fine a few days ago.
It's funny, but tragic.
Before you know it, someone's gone.
In Kuma's case,
he doesn't even realize he was ever human,
so the poor sap might as well be dead.
Now he's just a monster who the
government has do their dirty work.
It's the latest, the greatest, PASSA
FISTA, Pucci, your new old friend.
Kuma, what's the big idea?
You better stop shooting that
laser crap at me right now!
Yeah, I remember.
We will never meet again.
Farewell.
Even then, he knew.
What's wrong, Kuma?
Surely you recognize me?
That was spooky. Now where is he?
Hey, watch out, you guys! Get away!
Pad cannon.
Damn it, Kuma!
That's enough!
You forgot me!
But how about my face spectrum?
This ring a bell?
How about this?
Galaxy wing!
Oh, how dare you attack my sweet,
succulent crew of candy boys? You can!
I don't take unfashionable gestures
lightly, you conniving minks!
Vengeful care!
I have met a lot of people,
but no one forgets my face!
No one has ever forgotten
my face in my entire life!
This manga is damn favorable!
Kuma!
If you want to forget who you
are, that's your business.
But if you can't remember how
dangerous the great Ivankov is,
then I will beat it into you!
So get ready, hon!
He is pissed.
I'll take it from here.
All right, my battling beauties, keep
going and back Straw Boy up, okay?
Roger!
Okay, Straw Boy, let's get him.
Thanks, good luck!
Come on, ladies, get to the scaffold!
Ah!
Starhat's gonna steal all my thunder!
Now commence Operation Ming, Captain
Buggy, the king of the pirates!
Anything that's possible
with me at the helm!
The whole world will be taking it
back with my onslaught of awesomeness!
All of you, follow my lead
and don't mess anything up!
Forward, you fools! Ah!
I question the efficacy
of your latest strategy!
They're too many.
I won't reach him like this.
Don't you even dream of touching our pops?
Get out of my way.
What a pain in the ass.
He's going to mess up our rescue mission.
I call this brilliant punk!
He's fast. Too fast.
And strong.
Quite a combination for someone that size.
Congrats on your escape
from prison, Katorea Boy.
So, did you enjoy the pool
of blood during your stay?
Doflamingo, keep out
of my business or else.
It's not your concern.
Just making small talk.
So, listen, I think we
might make a good team.
Stop right there!
Yeah, you missed!
Half clear, Straw Hat!
Nice one!
Apologies, Shanks.
But I will not hold back against him.
Hey, I know him!
I wonder what is written.
Will my hand wipe his name from history?
Or perhaps his fortune shall spare him
the fury of this black sword I wield.